{
    "id": "c4822fa87a254b109483f2dbbd8bcd81",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I would rather you ………………. home now.",
            "description": "After would rather, we use a past tense to refer to the present.",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "went"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3c6326b047c34403bf705d15b01abfc6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am going to tell her a few facts about ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "herself"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1a1ec38a88d24512a60e2dc19f4120a5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you ever met the people ………………. live next door?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b6ab4a0138d44527862efcabb437c286"
        },
        {
            "question": "He got married again a year later, ………………….. surprised everybody.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "what",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e8eeea7a46f24249a8280a50da134ab8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw a girl …………………. beauty took my breath away.",
            "description": "Who's means who is or who has. Whose is the possessive word.",
            "answers": [
                "who's",
                "whose"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b8967155bdb2415a8def0a017c05ddd2"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is married to a singer ...................... you may have heard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whom",
                "of whom",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "168d08ff8db741e68829d89210c5bc9f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will give you ………………….. help I can.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3efbe1e2a3ee4b2699df5bbd0e2db659"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. she said made me angry.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "That"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f211bd0635a14f23a7e7c34f87ebc062"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please remind me .....................… to the post office.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of going",
                "to go"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6e454d7ff4b8485eb8c11bdc3d5136bb"
        },
        {
            "question": "She said that she ………………. enough.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "had",
                "had had"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5d2aea9181c44e55b986c8a8a70792e0"
        }
    ]
}